(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
僕たちは配信アプリ『ホロキャス』で活動する配信者。
We are streamers active on the streaming app 'HoloCas'.
突然画面に吸い込まれて、アプリと繋がる謎の世界『ホロキャス界』に来ちゃった。
We were suddenly sucked into the screen and ended up in a mysterious world connected to the app, 'HoloCas World'.
そこでは、現実で苦しむ人の魂が怪物化してしまう現象、『夢落ち』が起こっていた。
There, a phenomenon called 'Dreamfall' was occurring, where the souls of people suffering in reality turned into monsters.
怪物コラプサーを倒して、みんなの魂を取り戻さないと。
We have to defeat the monster 'Corruptor' and get everyone's souls back.
そして、魔法少女に変身して、戦うことになった。
And so, we transformed into magical girls and decided to fight.
みんなの心を助けて、夢を応援する！
I'll save everyone's hearts and support their dreams!
それが...
That is...
魔法少女ホロウィッチ！
Magical Girl Holo Witch!
今日はスペシャルハロウィンステージ！
Today is the Special Halloween Stage!
ホロキャスの人気配信者が多数出演！
Many popular HoloCas streamers will appear!
さらに、今をときめく超人気歌手の加納さんも参加する、超・超豪華イベント！
Plus, it's a super, super luxurious event that even the currently trending super-popular singer, Kano-san, is participating in!
で、その超豪華イベントのオープニングアクトを、うちら6人が担当することになって。
And the six of us were put in charge of the opening act for that super luxurious event.
せっかくだし、みんなでホロウィッチの衣装を着て、ドカンと派手に盛り上げちゃおうかなって！
Since it's a special occasion, I thought we'd all wear our Holo Witch costumes and really liven things up with a bang!
でもいいのかな？魔法とか、妖精とか、一応内緒なんだけど。
But is it okay? Magic, fairies, and all that... it's supposed to be a secret.
今日はハロウィンだから、仮装ってことにすれば、なんとかなるなる！
Since it's Halloween today, if we just say it's a costume, it'll work out somehow!
そうそう。
Right, right.
ってそろそろ準備したほうがよくね？
Don't you think we should start getting ready soon?
そうだね！じゃあ、気合入れていきますか！
You're right! Well then, let's give it our all!
トリック・オア...
Trick or...
トリート！
Treat!
ねっちゅー、ねっちゅー、ねっちゅー、足りないでしょ？
Netchu, netchu, netchu, it's not enough, right?
こっちおいで遊ぼうよ。
Come over here, let's play.
イライラしてイライラして 楽しくいられるための条件
Getting irritated, getting irritated, the condition for being able to have fun
イライラしてイライラして 魂抜ける もったいない
Getting irritated, getting irritated, losing your soul, what a waste
どうしたら喜んでくれるかな さあ 思いついては即行動 スマイルハンター
How can I make you happy? Now, act immediately upon thinking of it, Smile Hunter.
こっそり君のツボ ピンポイント撃ち抜いちゃうぞ お手柄
I'll secretly shoot through your weak spot precisely. Good job.
魔法だもん 愛の呪文 ホロキャスで コンサート
It's magic, you see. A spell of love. On HoloCas, a concert.
まだまだ仕掛けちゃえ
Let's keep on setting things up!
あっちゅう間に捕まえた
Caught you in no time!
ねっちゅー、ねっちゅー、ねっちゅーシンドローム いたずらからのハピネス
Netchu, netchu, Netchu Syndrome. Happiness from a prank.
ねっちゅー、ねっちゅー、ねっちゅーしたらギュって熱く自然にスマイルに
Netchu, netchu, if you do netchu, naturally you'll smile with a hot hug.
年中無休カーニバル 好き重なれば 年中無休カーニバル お祭り
Year-round carnival. If likes overlap, year-round carnival festival.
ねっちゅー、ねっちゅー、ねっちゅー足りない こっちおいで遊ぼうよ
Netchu, netchu, netchu is not enough. Come over here, let's play.
トリコにしちゃうわ ほらね
I'll make you a captive, see?
舞台は完璧 アドレナリン ドバドバ出させちゃうんです
The stage is perfect. I'll make the adrenaline gush out.
告白したらみんなが...
If I confess, everyone will...
ちょっと待って、私の出番は？
Wait a minute, where's my turn?
あ、いいよいいよ
Ah, it's fine, it's fine.
もうハチャメチャだ
It's already a mess.
弾む街彩っても 同じ道行く
Even if the bouncing town is colored, we walk the same path.
響き合って集まれば つまり最強じゃん！
If we resonate and gather, in other words, we're the strongest!
ねっちゅー、ねっちゅー、ねっちゅーシンドローム 逆上りすぎて白熱
Netchu, netchu, Netchu Syndrome. Overheating too much, glowing hot.
ねっちゅー、ねっちゅー、ねっちゅーしちゃお 変わって大きな Win-Win ハイ！
Netchu, netchu, let's do netchu. Changing into a big Win-Win. High!
異世界から 見せたいよ 精一杯の愛
I want to show you from another world, with all my love.
こんなにも近くにいるよ
I'm this close to you.
年中無休で笑いたい 君と笑い合いたいの
I want to smile year-round. I want to smile together with you.
ヨヨヨヨしていたら いつの間にか救えちゃう 幸せすぎて困っちゃう
If I'm doing 'yo-yo-yo', before I know it, I can save you. I'm so happy it's troubling.
捕まえたら離さない
Once I catch you, I won't let go.
ねっちゅー、ねっちゅー、ねっちゅーシンドローム いたずらからのハピネス
Netchu, netchu, Netchu Syndrome. Happiness from a prank.
ねっちゅー、ねっちゅー、ねっちゅーしたらギュって熱く自然にスマイルに
Netchu, netchu, if you do netchu, naturally you'll smile with a hot hug.
年中無休カーニバル 好き重なれば 年中無休カーニバル お祭り
Year-round carnival. If likes overlap, year-round carnival festival.
ねっちゅー、ねっちゅー、ねっちゅー足りない こっちおいで遊ぼうよ
Netchu, netchu, netchu is not enough. Come over here, let's play.
トリコにしちゃうわ ほらね
I'll make you a captive, see?
魔法少女 ホロウィッチ！
THE STAGE ～TRICK or MAGIC！～
Magical Girl HoloWitch!
THE STAGE ~TRICK or MAGIC!~
トリック・オア・トリート！
Trick or Treat!
みんなー盛り上がってるー？
Is everyone pumped up?!
ホロウィッチのオープニングアクト、どうだった？
How was the HoloWitch opening act?
ここからもっと、もっと盛り上げていくのら！
We're going to hype things up even more from here!
みんなで一緒に楽しもうね！
Let's all have fun together!
今日は我々、ホロキャスの配信者だけでなく...
Today, it's not just us HoloCas streamers...
...あの超人気歌手、カノンさんがゲストで来てくださっています！
...that super popular singer, Kanon-san, is here as our guest!
カノンさん、どうぞ！
Kanon-san, please!
トリック・オア・トリート。
Trick or treat.
みんな、今日は最後まで、よろしく。
Everyone, let's have a great time until the end today.
いや、まさか、あのカノンさんと同じステージに立てるとは...
Wow, I never imagined I'd stand on the same stage as Kanon-san...
いや、本当。憧れですよ。
I know, right. He's such an inspiration.
カノンさんの歌を聞くと、すっごくパワーもらえるのら。
Hearing Kanon-san sing gives me so much power!
そうそう。こんなにいただいちゃっていいんですかー？ってくらいね。
Exactly. It's like, "Are we allowed to receive this much?"
うん、めっちゃ元気出るよね。
Yeah, it really cheers you up.
ありがとう。なんでもないから。
Thank you. It's nothing.
次の曲は、みんなも一緒に歌ってほしいのら！
We want everyone to sing along for the next song!
君たち、遠慮しないで声出してね、声！
You guys, don't be shy, let's hear those voices!
じょいふる
作詞・作曲：水野良樹
Joyful
Lyrics & Composition: Yoshiki Mizuno
君の声を聞かせて
Let me hear your voice
さあ冒険してみない？
Why not go on an adventure?
楽しいこと始めよう
Let's start something fun
遊びたい (ぜったい)
I want to play (for sure)
したい (たい・たい・たい)
I want to (want-want-want)
逢いたい
I want to see you
the Joy the Joy the Joy
とびきりのベイビー
An extraordinary baby
Joy the Joy the Joy
とハッピーなピーポー
And happy people
弱虫なんかじゃない
I'm no coward
自信ありデシサイド
I've decided with confidence
君の瞳にキスして
Kissing your eyes
笑いたい (ぜったい)
I want to laugh (for sure)
したい (たい・たい・たい)
I want to (want-want-want)
逢いたい
I want to see you
the Joy the Joy the Joy
とごきげんベイビー
And a cheerful baby
Joy the Joy the Joy
とハッピーなセイヤー
And a happy sayer
君の心はぞんざい
Your heart is neglected
もっとギューギュー
Tighter and tighter
僕の心はそんざい
My heart exists
いっそグーグー
Maybe just sleep
弾けてるんじゃない？
Isn't it bursting?
いつJoyful
Always Joyful
ハピぺぽパプー
Hapi Pepo Papu
Joy the Joy the Joy
とびきりのベイビー
An extraordinary baby
Joy the Joy the Joy
とハッピーなセイヤー
And a happy sayer
ドキドキしちゃうのなんでだろ
Why is my heart racing?
ズキズキしちゃうのなんでだろ
Why is it aching?
輝く夢に捕まるのは
Being caught by a shining dream
どんな運命なんだろ
What kind of fate is it?
尽くしたいの
I want to give my all
Joyfulだけ終わっちゃう
Will it end with just Joyful?
Everybody 一言笑っちゃう
Everybody laughs with a word
いついつまでもこの時まで
Forever and ever, until this moment
最終回はきっと修正なしで
The finale will surely be unedited
(ドゥ・ウィ・ドゥ・ドゥ)
(Do we do do)
テンポハッピーぺぽ
Tempo happy pepo
したい (たい・たい・たい)
I want to (want-want-want)
逢いたい
I want to see you
the Joy the Joy the Joy
とごきげんベイビー
And a cheerful baby
Joy the Joy the Joy
とハッピーなセイヤー
And a happy sayer
君の心はぞんざい
Your heart is neglected
もっとギューギュー
Tighter and tighter
僕の心はそんざい
My heart exists
いっそグーグー
Maybe just sleep
弾けてるんじゃない？
Isn't it bursting?
いつJoyful
Always Joyful
ハピぺぽパプー
Hapi Pepo Papu
Joy!
そ、みんな、一緒に歌ってくれて、ありがとう!
So, everyone, thank you for singing along with me!
いやー、よかったねー。
Wow, that was great.
会場がね、一体になったって感じでね。
It felt like the whole venue became one.
うん。
Yeah.
よかったよかった。
I'm so glad.
テンション上がるわーこれ!
This really gets me pumped up!
さ、さて次は、いよいよ、カノンさんに歌っていただきます。
N-now, next, at last, Kanon-san will be singing for us.
君、大丈夫?
Are you okay?
あ、何?
Ah, what?
何なの?
What's going on?
何の音?
What was that sound?
取れないんだけど...
I can't get it off...
何これ?!
What is this?!
ちょ、ちょ、ちょ、ちょ、ちょ、何何? どういうこと?
W-w-w-wait, what's happening? What does this mean?
コラプサーだ。
It's a Kolapsar.
ですよね。どう考えてもね。
I thought so. No matter how you look at it.
コラプサー... やっぱり。
Kolapsar... I knew it.
顔面がデンプンになってるよ!
Her face is turning into starch!
フブさん!
Fubu-san!
フブさん、出てる出てる。魂のモツが出てたな!
Fubu-san, it's coming out. Her soul's innards were coming out!
うっ... コラプサーが出てくるってことは、夢落ちしてる人がいるんだ、多分。
Ugh... If Kolapsars are appearing, it means there's someone falling into a nightmare... probably.
ミオ先輩!
Mio-senpai!
ミオちゃん!
Mio-chan!
ご、ごめん。うち、うち...
S-sorry. I, I...
うち、本当は...
Actually, I...
黒いのカボチャが、怖くてダメなの。
I'm terrified of those black pumpkins.
えー?!
Ehhh?!
ちっちゃい頃、パパが、ハロウィンで、あれ被って帰ってきて...
When I was little, my dad came home wearing one of those for Halloween...
ただいまー
I'm home!
うち、パパがカボチャに食べられちゃったんだって、思っちゃって。
I thought my dad had been eaten by the pumpkin.
ハッピーハロウィーン!!
Happy Halloween!!
それから、どうしても...
And ever since then...
ハロウィンのカボチャだけは、無理なのー!
I just can't handle Halloween pumpkins!
いやぁー!
Nooo!
チェンジ!
Change!
ガーディアンアーム!
Guardian Arm!
巫女ベルロッド!
Miko Bell Rod!
キャンディーパラソル!
Candy Parasol!
ガンバリーナー!
Gun-ba-rina-!
スノーフレークセイバー!
Snowflake Saber!
フブキマル!
Fubukimaru!
ここは任せて、ミオ!
Leave this to us, Mio!
みんな...
Everyone...
魔法、みんなに見せちゃうけど、いいよね?
I'm going to show everyone my magic, is that okay?
うん、そんなこと言ってられないし!
Yeah, we don't have time to worry about that!
だよね。夢落ちした人を助ける。それが...
Right. Saving those who fall into a nightmare. That's...
魔法少女ホロウィッチ!
Magical Girl Holowitch!
この手を差し伸べ、掴んで、握る。天子のホロ、魔法少女かなた!
Reach out, catch, and hold. Holo of the Angel, Magical Girl Kanata!
みんなの願いを咲かせる祈り。巫女のホロ、魔法少女みこ!
The prayer that makes everyone's wishes bloom. Holo of the Shrine Maiden, Magical Girl Miko!
甘い幸せお裾分け。姫のホロ、魔法少女ルーナ!
Sharing a sweet happiness. Holo of the Princess, Magical Girl Luna!
煌めくお宝ロックオン! 海賊のホロ、魔法少女マリン!
Locking on to sparkling treasure! Holo of the Pirate, Magical Girl Marine!
心躍らすトリックスター。狐のホロ、魔法少女フブキ!
The heart-stirring trickster. Holo of the Fox, Magical Girl Fubuki!
曇りなき純白の愛。雪のホロ。
Crystal-clear pure white love. Holo of Snow.
魔法少女ラミィ！
Magical Girl Lamy!
ホロウィッチ！
HoloWitch!
フルキャスト！
Full Cast!
いくよー！
Here I go!
ほい！
Hah!
よい！
Ho!
はい！
Hya!
パンプン。
Pampun.
敵じゃないよ。仲間だよ。
Not an enemy. A comrade.
こん！
Kon!
やめな。
Stop it.
えい！
Hah!
ね、なんかこれまずくない？どんどん強くなってる。
Hey, isn't this bad? They're getting stronger and stronger.
みんなが奴らを倒すより、
It seems like anxiety and fear
不安と恐れが膨れ上がる方が早いみたい。
are growing faster than everyone can defeat them.
そんな...
No way...
うちのせい...
It's my fault...
うちがあんなもの怖いって思っちゃうせいで...
It's because I'm so scared of those things...
そんなこと...
That's not...
わかってるの。
I know.
おかしいよね。あんなのがこんなどうしようもなく怖いなんて。
It's weird, right? To be so helplessly scared of something like that.
だから、今日も我慢して、頑張ろうって思ったのに。
That's why I thought I'd endure it today and do my best.
でも...
But...
でもやっぱり...
but I still...
おかしくなんてないよ。
It's not weird at all.
カノンさん？
Kanon-san?
誰にだって苦手なものがある。
Everyone has things they're not good at.
怖いもの、嫌いなもの。
Things they fear, things they dislike.
人に「なんでそんなものが」って言われても、
There are things you just can't help,
どうしようもないことってやっぱりあるよ。
even if people ask why.
そうだよ！
That's right!
何が苦手とか何が怖いかとかは関係なくて！
It doesn't matter what you're bad at or what you're afraid of!
大事なのは、今みおちゃんが辛いって思ってるかどうかだから！
What matters is whether or not Mio-chan is hurting right now!
遠慮しないで、
Don't hesitate,
頼ってほしいのら。
we want you to rely on us.
だってうちら、お互い様じゃん！
Because we're all in this together!
誰かの辛さ、誰かの苦手は、
Someone's pain or weakness
他の誰かがカバーする。お互いそうやって、
can be covered by someone else. That's how we,
やってきたから、今がある。
made it to where we are today.
こんなに頑張れる。もっと！
I can try this hard. Even more!
ホロウィッチ。コラプターは夢落ちした人の恐れと不安から生まれ、
HoloWitch. Corruptors are born from the fear and anxiety of those who have lost their dreams,
その心を深く沈ませてしまう。
and they cause their hearts to sink deep down.
夢落ちって、どうしてそれを？
Lost their dreams? How do you know that?
でも、私は知ってる。君たちなら、ホロウィッチなら、
But I know. If it's you, if it's HoloWitch,
辛い、苦しい、悲しい、きつい。
Pain, suffering, sadness, hardship.
そんな自分一人の力じゃ抜け出せない暗闇の中にいても、
Even in a darkness you can't escape on your own,
夢と、光を届けてくれる。
you will deliver dreams and light.
任せて！
Leave it to us!
さあ、みんな。ホロウィッチが戦ってくれる。
Now, everyone. HoloWitch is fighting for us.
では、私たちにできるのは。そう、私たちの声で、思いで、彼女たちを応援することだ。
So, what we can do is... yes, to support them with our voices and our feelings.
いざ、トリック・オア・トリート！
Now, Trick or Treat!
「仮装狂騒曲」
"Kasou Kyousoukyoku"
作詞：TOPHAMHAT-KYO (FAKE TYPE.) 作曲：FAKE TYPE.
Lyrics: TOPHAMHAT-KYO (FAKE TYPE.) Composition: FAKE TYPE.
あれよと言う間に飲み込まれ
Swallowed up in the blink of an eye
代々色のタイダルウェーブ やっこい やっこい
An orange tidal wave, soft and gentle
ハンドメイドからオーダーメイドまで 仕掛ける大流行
From handmade to order-made, a great fashion setting in
有象無象から見せもんを まとめて大集合
A grand gathering of spectacles from the masses
ソレもコレもと不条理な世界に お揃いの良い加減でッケケキな
This and that in an absurd world, with a matching good measure, it's spooky
これもよしの奴隷よ ドッシリとれよ
You're a slave to this too, take it easy
条理式 ポーション ホップ トゥ レイン
Rational potion, hop to rain
テールかヘッドか 占い合戦
Tail or head? A fortune-telling battle
自由に踊って 占い合戦
Dance freely, a fortune-telling battle
チヤホヤしたりされたりがいいでしょう 前代未聞の 鳴り響く
It's good to be pampered or pamper others, right? An unprecedented resonance
チョコにしちゃって 投げ捨てるベイビー 限界突破さ 手に取れ
Turn it into chocolate and throw it away, baby. Break through the limits, take it in hand
君のませ　制御不能の
Your precocious, uncontrollable
ユニバーサル　エギマイナス　エギパイルド
Universal egi-minus egi-piled
ユニバーサル　イミニミニマニモー
Universal eeny, meeny, miny, moe
恐ろしな　ぞろぞろ　ハロー
Terrifying, streaming in, hello
上がり上がり回る　月に針が落ちる　ワー
Rising and spinning, the needle drops on the moon, wah!
おひなくちゃで笑う　カボチャたち　一旦　モー
Pumpkins laughing in a mess, for now, moo!
それが合図　魔物たちが目覚め踊る　ワー
That's the signal, the monsters wake up and dance, wah!
こうなれば　あとは思いのまま
Now that it's come to this, let it go as you wish
ホー！ロー！
Ho! Lo!
骨抜きダンサボー
Spineless danceable
スケアクロウも飛び跳ね回る
The scarecrow is also jumping around
ホー！ロー！
Ho! Lo!
奇妙なタンテボー
Strange turntable
くるくる回る　美味しさ高まる
Round and round it goes, the deliciousness grows
ウィーガッタパーティーナイト！
We gotta party night!
エニウェイ　ジョインザパーティーナイト
Anyway, join the party night
不気味なプーカ　じゃっくらなクーカ　邪も無理　ムリ
Eerie Pooka, Jack-o'-Lantern-ish Kooka, even evil is impossible, impossible
セダカニセダカは　チェイスなしで
High and low, without a chase
蓋開け　ヘラヘラ　ゲラゲラ　ヘリヤ　ヤー
Open the lid, laughing, chuckling, hey-ya-ya
オズマの素敵なナイト　見つからなくても既に話題だ
Ozma's wonderful night, even if not found, it's already a topic
風変わりなカキグルミ　島風から入るキリリリリ　ユッピー
Strange costume, coming in from the island breeze, kiriririri, yippie!
仮の正体も魂の本物ならば　魅了しちゃうな　ジョー
If the temporary identity is the true soul, I'll be charmed, Joe
知らぬ一両　さあ参りましょう
One vehicle unknown, now let's go
霧のみぼん　火の日に　ジョン
Foggy ribbon, on a fire day, John
ガラパゴスに交わる異世界
Another world mingling with Galapagos
ダイコオリパーティー　メイヤー！
Great ice party mayor!
振り切れる鼓動　ハロー
A heart that beats fast, hello
悪辣なドラキュラ　お酒を煽る　ワー
Wicked Dracula, guzzling alcohol, wah!
カマ臭なデュラハン　頭を振る　ワー
Flashy Dullahan, shaking his head, wah!
紳士的なミイラすらも服がはだける　ワー
Even a gentlemanly mummy gets his clothes disheveled, wah!
どうあれど愉快全開のまま
No matter what, stay in full high spirits
本性　あらわにあれよ
Let your true self be revealed
その仮装にも正装になろう
Let that costume become your formal wear
狂騒曲のタンテボー
Rhapsody's turntable
合い合い回る　美味しさ高まる
Spinning together, the deliciousness grows
ウィーガッタパーティーナイト！
We gotta party night!
ハイファイ　オールナイト　オールナイト
Hi-fi all night, all night
眠れやしない　ウララララ
Can't sleep, ulalalala
フライハイ　オールナイト　オールナイト
Fly high all night, all night
鳴り止まない　ウララララ
It won't stop ringing, ulalalala
小粋なソラアソビ
Stylish sky play
ランタンはまるで魂
The lantern is like a soul
以全奇奇怪怪ジャンボリー
Evermore bizarre jamboree
闇に寄せ　ハロウィン
Approaching the darkness, Halloween
ホー！ロー！
Ho! Lo!
骨抜きダンサボー
Spineless danceable
スケアクロウも飛び跳ね回る
The scarecrow is also jumping around
ホー！ロー！
Ho! Lo!
奇妙なタンテボー
Strange turntable
くるくる回る　美味しさ高まる
Round and round it goes, the deliciousness grows
ウィーガッタパーティーナイト！
We gotta party night!
エニウェイ　ジョインザパーティーナイト
Anyway, join the party night
くるくる回る　美味しさ高まる
Round and round it goes, the deliciousness grows
ウィーガッタパーティーナイト　ナイ　ナイ
We gotta party night, night, night
ホロウィッチの力が乱れてる！
HoloWitch's power is going haywire!
恐れと不安が溶けていくんだ。
The fear and anxiety are melting away.
歌の力、
With the power of song,
みんなの声の力で！
with the power of everyone's voices!
ホロウィッチ頑張って！
Do your best, HoloWitch!
みんな乗ってるね！
Everyone's into it!
ホロウィッチのみんな、頑張れ！
Go for it, HoloWitch!
おかげでこっちもやる気いっぱいなのな！
Thanks to that, I'm fully motivated too!
さあ、行って、ホロウィッチ！
Now, go, HoloWitch!
心を苛むトリックに、
To the tricks that torment hearts,
とびっきりのトリートを！
give them an extra special treat!
みんな、応援ありがとう！
Everyone, thanks for the support!
思う存分、楽しんじゃうよ！
I'm going to enjoy this to the fullest!
トリッキー、行け！
Tricky, go!
イノセントリバイバー！
Innocent Reviver!
信じるからね！
Because I believe!
みんなの愛が力をくれる！
Everyone's love gives me strength!
おらあ！
Take this!
ふぶにゃん！
Fubunyan!
ラミィちゃんナイス！
Lamy-chan, nice!
それじゃあ、決めちゃうよ！
Now then, let's finish this!
ユニリーアラミネーション！
Unilley Allamination!
スラッシュドームコンプレッサー！
Slash Dome Compressor!
はあ！
Ha!
えいやあ！
Eiya!
みこみこせんぱーい！
Miko-Miko Senpai!
サンキューうなたん！
Thank you, Luna-tan!
トリック・オア・スフィア！
Trick or Sphere!
みんなみこのエリートなとこ、そんなに見たいんだ。
Everyone, you want to see Miko's elite side that much?
しょうがないね。
Can't be helped, then.
みんなと一緒に...
Together with everyone...
...ルナマジカルなのら！
...it's Luna Magical, nora!
ハイパーサクラビウムセイバー！
Hyper Sakurabium Saber!
プリンセスセイバー！
Princess Saber!
スラッシュヘイロー！
Slash Halo!
サンキューかなたん！
Thank you, Kanatan!
みんなの思い、全部のっけて...
Carrying everyone's feelings...
...飛び込んでいくしかないだろ！
...I've just got to dive in!
君たち、ちょうどいいとこに来てくれるじゃん。
You guys arrived at just the right time.
みんなそろって、いいお宝ね！
All of you together, what a great treasure!
よっしゃー！
Alright!
セレスティアル・リンギング！
Celestial Ringing!
オーバースラッシュ・ヘイロー！
Over Slash Halo!
あいつらでラストだ！
Those guys are the last!
今だよ、みんな！
Now's the time, everyone!
チェンジ！ホロウィッチステッキ！
Change! Hollowitch Stick!
ウィッチグラム！
Witch Gram!
フルキャスト！
Full Cast!
ミオ先輩、もう大丈夫そう？
Mio-senpai, do you seem okay now?
あ、うん。
Ah, yeah.
その...見ないようにすればなんとか。
Well... as long as I don't look, I can manage.
わかるよ。白上も高いとこ行くと下見れないからね。
I understand. Shirakami can't look down when in high places either.
うなたんも、虫はなるべく見ないようにしてるのら。
Luna-tan also tries not to look at bugs as much as possible.
ありがとう、みんな。
Thank you, everyone.
みんなが助けてくれたみたいに、
Just like everyone helped me,
うちも、みんなが辛い時、苦しい時があったら、
I, too, if you all have painful or difficult times,
絶対、絶対に力になるから！
I'll definitely, definitely be there for you!
さて、これでめでたしめでたし。でもいいんだけど...
Now, this would be a happy ending. Which is fine, but...
みんな！ホロウィッチの活躍、もっと見たいんじゃない？
Everyone! Don't you want to see more of Holowitch in action?
見たいー！見たいー！
We do! We do!
だそうだけど...
So they say...
やぁあああああ...！
Yaaaaaaaa...!
えっ、こっち？
Eh, here?
こっち振るの？えっ、あ、や...
I'm supposed to swing it here? Wait, uh...
やりまーす！
I'll do it!
よーし！やるよーみんなー！
Alright! Let's do this, everyone!
おー！
Yeah!
RPG
作詞：Saori, Fukase 作曲：Fukase
Lyrics: Saori, Fukase Composition: Fukase
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue
海を目指して歩く
We walk toward the sea
怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be afraid of
僕らはもう一人じゃない
Because we're not alone anymore
大切な何かが
When something precious
壊れたあの夜に
Was broken on that night
私は星を探して
I went looking for the stars
一人で歩いていた
And walked all by myself
ペルセウス座に群れ
Gathering at Perseus
君も見てただろうか
Were you watching too?
僕ら元気にやってるよ
We're doing just fine
君は今どこにいるの？
Where are you now?
方法という悪魔に
By the demon called 'Method'
惑わされないで
Don't be led astray
目的という大事な
But remember that important
ものを思い出して
Thing called 'Purpose'
フゥー！
Woo!
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue
海を目指して歩く
We walk toward the sea
怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be afraid of
僕らはもう一人じゃない
Because we're not alone anymore
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue
海を目指して歩く
We walk toward the sea
怖くても大丈夫
Even if it's scary, it's okay
僕らはもう一人じゃない
Because we're not alone anymore
Yeah!
大切な何かが
When something precious
壊れたあの夜に
Was broken on that night
私は君を探して
I went looking for you
一人で歩いていた
And walked all by myself
あの日から僕らは
Since that day, we've each
一人で海を目指す
Headed for the sea alone
約束のあの場所で
But at that promised place
必ずまた会おう
We'll surely meet again
世間という悪魔に
By the demon called 'Society'
惑わされないで
Don't be led astray
自分だけが決めた
But remember the answer
答えを思い出して
That you decided for yourself
フゥー！
Woo!
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue
海を目指して歩く
We walk toward the sea
怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be afraid of
僕らはもう一人じゃない
Because we're not alone anymore
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue
海を目指して歩く
We walk toward the sea
怖くても大丈夫
Even if it's scary, it's okay
僕らはもう一人じゃない
Because we're not alone anymore
空は青く澄み渡り…
The sky is clear and blue...
海を目指して歩く
Walking toward the sea
怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be afraid of
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are no longer alone
空は青く澄み渡り…
The sky is clear and blue...
海を目指して歩く
Walking toward the sea
怖くても大丈夫
It's okay to be afraid
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are no longer alone
みんな、今日はありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for today!
最高に楽しいハロウィンだったよね、みんな！
It was the best Halloween ever, right everyone?
ちょっとアクシデントもあったけどさ、そういうのも含めて、
There were some accidents too, but including that...
いいお宝… いい思い出になったんじゃない？
...wasn't it a great treasure... a great memory?
さて、そろそろお時間となって参りましたが…
Now, it's almost time to say goodbye, but...
アンコール！ アンコール！
Encore! Encore!
それじゃあアンコールにお答えして、
Well then, in response to the encore,
この曲歌っちゃうのら！
Let's sing this song!
はじまりの魔法-charm-
The Beginning of Magic -charm-
作詞・作曲・編曲：三好啓太
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Keita Miyoshi
君に魔法をかけるよ ミケセルオマジ
I'll cast a spell on you, Miketseru Omaji
始まりを告げる
Announcing the beginning
衝動が響く
The impulse resounds
気づいた時がいつだってスタートラインなんだ
Whenever you notice it, that's your starting line
何者でもなかった
Who used to be nobody
君を変えたのは
What changed you was
見つけたばかりのちっぽけな輝きの原石
A tiny rough diamond of radiance you just found
どうして私だけ上手くいかないんだろう
Why am I the only one who can't do things right?
自分以外のすべてが眩しく見えるけど
Everything except myself looks dazzling
ねぇ 君に見つけてほしくて
Hey, I wanted you to find me
なりたい私になる 今こそ
I'll become who I want to be, starting now
そうさ 叶えたい 掴みたい 夢があるから
Yes, because I have a dream I want to fulfill and grasp
塞ぎ込んだ昨日ごと連れて踏み出すんだ
I'll take all my gloomy yesterdays and step forward
信じる力が奇跡を起こすように
So the power of belief can work a miracle
君に魔法をかけるよ ミケセルオマジ
I'll cast a spell on you, Miketseru Omaji
数多の望み
Countless hopes
叶わない願い
Unfulfilled wishes
それぞれが等しく 混ざり合ってく世界で
In a world where they all blend together equally
何を求めて 歩き続けるんだろう
What are we searching for as we keep walking?
いつまでこの場所に迷うけど
We get lost in this place forever, but
君がくれたこの空が
This sky that you gave me
癒えない翼をくれたね
Gave me wings that will never fail
そうさ 照らしたい 届けたい 人がいるから
Yes, because there's someone I want to shine for, to reach
もう一人置いていったりしないと決めたんだ
I've decided not to leave anyone alone anymore
愛したい 応えたい 自分自身の意思
I want to love, I want to respond, by my own will
正解なんてこれでいい 見たい景色を背に
This is the right answer, with the view I want to see behind me
どんな場所でもいいよ
Any place is fine
どんな姿でもいい
Any form is fine
追いかけたいんだ あの煌めきを
I want to chase after that sparkle
希望 光 力 連れて 抱きしめて持っていこう
Taking hope, light, and power, let's embrace them and go
ほら 繋げたい 広げたい 道があるから
Look, because there's a path I want to connect and expand
ここから始まる物語 一緒に歩こう
Let's walk together in the story that begins here
信じる力が奇跡を起こすように
So the power of belief can work a miracle
この…
This...
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a spell on you
We Can Spell Oh Yeah
最高のステージだったよ、ホロウィッチ
That was an amazing performance, HoloWitch!
本当、本当！
It really was!
みんな、お疲れ様
Good job, everyone!
カノンさん、あの...
Kanon-san, um...
今日は本当にありがとうございました
Thank you so much for everything today.
それで、あなたはどうして夢落ちとか僕たちのことを...
But, how do you know about the dream-fall and us...?
私、前に夢落ちして
Actually, I once fell into a dream-fall
君たちに助けられたことがあるんだ
and was saved by you all.
えええ！？
What!?
だから、あの時の自分と同じように
So, whenever I see someone else
夢落ちして苦しんでいる誰かを見ると、放っておけなくて
suffering from a dream-fall like I was, I can't just ignore it.
あと実は、今日このステージに出ることにしたのも
And to be honest, the reason I decided to appear on this stage
君たちが出ると聞いたからなんだ。もう一度会えたらって思って
was because I heard you'd be here. I wanted to see you again.
だから今日は、えっと... すごく嬉しかった
So today, um... I was really happy.
これからも頑張ってね、ホロウィッチ
Keep up the good work, HoloWitch!
それじゃ
See ya.
また！是非また！
Later! Definitely later!
あの人自身が夢落ちしてホロウィッチに助けられていたから
Since he was saved by HoloWitch! when he was in a dream-fall...
知っていたんだ
He understood.
夢落ちした時の辛さも
How painful a dream-fall is,
そんな時誰かが手を差し伸べてくれることの嬉しさも
and how happy it makes you when someone reaches out a hand.
そっか、みこたちが少しでも誰かの力になれたら
I see. If we can help someone even just a little bit,
その誰かが、また別の誰かの力になってくれるんだね
then that person can go on to help someone else.
そうだね
Exactly.
しかもさ、それだけじゃなくて、うちらの力になってくれたりもするわけじゃん
And it's not just that. They can also become a source of strength for us.
あの人や、今日応援してくれたみんなみたいに
Just like him, and like everyone who cheered for us today.
それって...
And that's...
それってすっごく...
And that's really...
すっごくトリート！
A total treat!
キラキラ宝石みたいに輝いて
Sparkling like a brilliant gem
夢の結晶は　皆の宝物
A crystal of dreams is everyone's treasure
時々見失っちゃうこともあるけど
Sometimes we lose sight of it
溢れ出した　光が僕を呼ぶんだよ
But the overflowing light calls out to me
絶対大丈夫　ただ真っ直ぐで
It'll be okay, just stay true
いることも楽じゃない日もあるよね
Though some days aren't so easy
諦めも　苦しみも　重ねていこう
Let's face the regrets and the pain together
心解き放とう
And set our hearts free
夢を歌を魔法に乗せて
Carry our dreams and songs on magic
何度だって立ち上がる　君と一緒に進んでいく
We'll stand up again and again, moving forward with you
キラリ光り出す魔法
Magic that begins to sparkle and shine
頑張ってみても
Even if you try your hardest
上手くいかない日の方が　多く感じちゃったりするよね
You might feel like there are more days when things don't go right
さあ、不安かな？　悲しみも
Now, are you feeling anxious? And sadness too?
抱えないで一人じゃない
Don't carry it alone, you're not by yourself
希望の種を　明日に撒いたら
If you sow the seeds of hope for tomorrow
一番に輝く綺麗な花が咲くよ
The most brilliant and beautiful flower will bloom
夢を　歌を　魔法に乗せて
Dreams and songs, carried on magic
ハイ！
Hey!
何度も立ち上がる　君と一緒に進んでいく
Standing up again and again, I'll move forward with you
夢は　夢は　まだ終わらない
The dream, the dream, it's not over yet
未来を取り戻そう
Let's take back the future
何度だって笑って　もう一回歩き始めよう
Laugh as many times as it takes, let's start walking once more
ホロウィッチ　おはよう　夢の先へ
HoloWitch, good morning, to the future beyond the dream
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much